Sketch is a adventure, fantasy, comedy film directed by Seth Worley.
When a young girl’s sketchbook falls into a strange pond, her
drawings come to life—chaotic, real, and on the loose.
As the town descends into chaos, her family must reunite and
stop the monsters they never meant to unleash.
Taylor Wyatt, played by Tony Hale.
Liz Wyatt, played by D'Arcy Carden.
Amber Wyatt, played by Bianca Belle.
Jack Wyatt, played by Kue Lawrence.
Bowman Lynch, played by Kalon Cox.
Demarcus, played by Jaxen Kenner.
Sketch is a 2024 American fantasy comedy horror film
written and directed by Seth Worley.
The film stars Tony Hale and D'Arcy Carden.
The film was released to theatres on August 6, 2025, and
received positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of based on short film, serene, amused, awestruck.
The tone is lighthearted.